# **Arkadiusz Sarach**

## Junior Front-End Developer



## **Personal Info**

## Email

arkadiusz.sarach@gmail.com

#### **Address**

Cracow

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/Ajek1993

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/arkadiusz-sarach/

#### Website

https://my-portoflio-mu.vercel.app/

#### **Skills**

Programming languages: JavaScript (Node.js), Typescript, CSS, SCSS

Frameworks/Libraries: React, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, NextUI, Express.js

IDE: Visual Studio Code

Other: Git, Firebase, MongoDB, ESLint, Postman

## Languages

English - B2

## **Hobby/Interest**

music (playing drums), literature (Sapkowski, Cejrowski, astronomy), sport (cycling), computer games Determined to change the industry to IT, I am constantly willing to develop and acquire new knowledge. I quickly learn technical issues and can effectively apply them in practice. Since I started learning, I have experienced great satisfaction from discovering new possibilities offered by the latest libraries and frameworks. This is an additional motivation for me to improve in this field. The most inspiring projects for me are those that make use of the potential of the latest technologies. I am particularly fascinated by creating working algorithms that solve problems.

# **Projects**

#### **Yoom - Zoom Clone**

https://github.com/Ajek1993/zoom-clone

Aplikacja działa tak samo jak Zoom.

Technologies: Next.js, Typescript, TailwindCSS, ESlint, git

## **Facebook Copy**

https://github.com/Ajek1993/facebook-copy

The application is similar to well-known social network (still in progress).

Technologies: Next.js, Typescript, TailwindCSS, Next UI, Firebase, Firestore, ESlint, OpenAI, git

#### Fleet Manager

https://github.com/Ajek1993/Fleet\_Manager

Web aplication to manage car's fleet - allows adding/removing cars, repairs, fuel, counting costs. Technologies: React, Material UI, Firebase, Firestore, git

## **Oddaj Rzeczy**

https://github.com/Ajek1993/OddajRzeczy

Node, is for programmers

Technologies: Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Firebase, Firestore, git

# **Education**

2023-12

	riouely for programmers
- 2024-02	Coders Lab - Szkoła IT
	Duration - 130 hours
2023-03 - 2023-10	Front-End-Developer
	Coders Lab - Szkoła IT
	Duration - 180 hours
2013-10	Mining geomechanics and underground construction, Master of
- 2018-10	Science

Akademia Górniczo-Hutnicza im. Stanisława Staszica, Kraków

## **Work History**

2019-07

- 2024-04	Stava S.A., Kraków
2017-04 - 2019-06	<b>Driver</b> Abacus Sp. z o.o., Kraków
2015-07 - 2015-08	<b>Intern</b> Polska Grupa Górnicza - KWK "Piast-Ziemowit" - Ruch Piast, Bieruń

**Branch supervisor** 

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie danych osobowych zawartych w niniejszym dokumenciedo realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochroniedanych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z RozporządzeniemParlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawieochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawieswobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).